Let's go on a tour of the Scikit Learn source code.
我们接下来开始浏览 scikit-learn 的源代码
This is really why I wanted you to learn
这就是为什么我希望你学习面向对象编程
object oriented programming and how to make a Python package.
以及如何制作 Python 软件包的原因
If you want to understand what packages like Pandas, SciPy,
如果你想要理解 Pandas SciPy
NumPy or Scikit-learn are doing,
NumPy 或者 scikit-learn 这些软件包
you need to understand at least the basics of object oriented programming.
至少需要理解面向对象编程的基础知识
As we go through the Scikit Learn source code,
当我们浏览 scikit-learn 源代码时
you'll see some things that are familiar based on what you've done in this lesson,
你会看到一些内容与这节课做的练习非常相似
including import statements, classes, and inheritance.
包括 import 语句 类和继承
You'll also notice syntax that we didn't cover such as the at symbol, mixins,
你也会注意到一些我们还没有涉及到的语法 比如 @ 符号、mixin
and cases of multiple inheritance,
以及多重继承的示例
where class inherits from two or more parent classes.
其中类继承于两个或多个父类
Object oriented programming is a big topic and
面向对象编程是非常大的课题
Python has a lot more functionality than what you've seen so far.
Python 拥有非常多你还未见过的功能
I'm going to open Google and search for Scikit-learn source code.
打开谷歌 搜索 scikit-learn 源代码
It turns out that the code is hosted on GitHub.
可以看到这些代码托管在 GitHub 上
Here's the repository.
这就是存储的代码库
Let's go into the sklearn folder and see what we can find.
打开 sklearn 文件夹 看看能发现什么
Okay. I see the linear model folder,
嗯 我看到了 linear_model 文件夹
which I'm guessing holds code for things like linear regression.
我猜其中存放了关于线性回归的代码
At the very top is a tests folder.
最上面是 tests 文件夹
You can see that writing test code is
可以看出编写测试代码
an important part of developing a Python package or really any program.
在 Python 软件包或者任何程序中都是重要的一部分
Opening up the test folder,
打开 tests 文件夹
you can explore all the different tests
可以浏览所有不同的测试
that have been written for different functionality.
针对各种不同的功能
Let's go back up to the linear model folder.
回到上一级 linear_model 文件夹
Since there's an init file,
因为这里有一个 init 文件
you know that linear model is actually a package.
你可以了解到 linear_model 实际上是一个软件包
Opening that file, this code should be somewhat familiar.
打开这个文件 代码看起来有些熟悉
The init file is importing the classes contained in each of the package modules.
init 文件导入了软件包每个模块中的类
This is equivalent to the init file in your distributions package where you
这等同于在 distributions 软件包的 init 文件中
were creating shortcuts to the class names. We can go back.
创建类名的快捷方式 再次返回
Now, I'll open based.py,
这次我们打开 base.py
and see what's inside.
看一下有什么代码
It starts off with a few comments and then there are a lot of import statements.
该文件的开头有一些注释 然后是很多 import 语句
So the base.py file is using a lot of other Python modules or packages.
所以 base.py 文件中使用了很多其他的模块或软件包
Next, there's a variable called sparse intercepts decay,
接下来是一个叫做 SPARSE_INTERCEPTS_DECAY 的变量
and a function called make dataset.
还有一个叫做 make_dataset 的函数
As I mentioned in the beginning of the lesson,
正如我在课程开始时提到的
a Python module can contain any combination of variables, functions, or classes.
Python 模块中可以包含变量、函数、类的任意组合
Scrolling down, this is where things get a little more advanced.
滚动向下 可以看到一些比较高级的内容
The at symbol is called a decorator,
这个 @ 符号被称为装饰器
and you might not have seen this before.
你可能还没有见过
I'll put a resource below the video if you want to learn about decorators.
如果你想要了解装饰器相关 可以参考下方的资料链接
I'm going to scroll down a bit more.
再向下滚动
Here we are with the first class in the module,
看到了模块中的第一个类
it's called Linear Model,
名称是 LinearModel
and the class inherits from two parent classes ABCmeta and BaseEstimato.
这个类继承自两个父类 ABCMeta 和 BaseEstimator
Then, you can see the linear model class has a few methods.
然后你可以看到 LinearModel 类有几个方法
The dash before the decision function is just a convention that usually indicates that
_decision_function 前面的下划线只是一种方便的用法
the function is only meant to be used internally
表示该函数仅在类内部使用
inside the class and not by an instantiated object.
而不是由实例化对象使用
If you want to get involved with contributing to a library like this,
如果你想要参与贡献这类软件库
check out the issues page,
请查看 Issues 页面
it's at the top of a GitHub page.
可以在 GitHub 页面的上部找到入口
Here's issues, I'm going to click on it.
这里就是 Issues 点击进去
You can read about the issues and see if there's something that you could contribute to.
你可以阅读有关问题的信息 看看是否有什么可以贡献
I'll also put a few links below giving
我也在下方给出了
guidelines about how to contribute to a GitHub project.
如何参与贡献 GitHub 项目的指导说明链接
Scikit Learn is a large package with a lot of code,
scikit-learn 是一个大型的软件包 其中包含了大量的代码
but don't get too overwhelmed.
但是不用觉得不知所措
Realize that a package like this was built over
你要意识到像这样的软件包是随着时间的推移而逐渐建立的
time with various people contributing to different parts,
各种各样的人都在为不同的部分做出贡献
but the basic package you coded in this lesson
在课程中编写的基础的软件包
is essentially how a much larger package works.
就是这种大型软件包工作的基本原理
You start small with just a few modules and over time,
你可以从仅有几个模块的小的软件包开始
you add more and more functionality.
随着时间的推移添加越来越多的功能